Thank you for watching!
Don! Here we go, Nogizaka Kenketsuichi, with our host, Bananaman.
Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you. Nogizaka-san.
Seino
BQ
BQ BQ BQ
Let's start today's program with an announcement!
Let's look back at the year 2023!
Nogizaka46 brought us a lot of news last year!
Let's take a look at some of the little news that happened to the Nogizaka46 members that went unnoticed.
First, let's take a look at the Nogizaka B News from January to May.
Discovering Tsutsuki Yoneda 2000
Umezawa ignored by his secular mother
Yamashita Freezing in Okinawa in Winter
Visiting Asuka Ogawa
Yumiki Valentine's Nightmare
Successfully photographed Yoda psychic phenomena
Kubo ghost photo taken
Nakanishi Takoyaki party incident
UmezawaSorry treatment for smart phone
TV to background Shokichi
Sato Rika Just in time for a roller coaster ride
Yakubo blends in at the University
That's all for the B-Nogizaka news from January to May.
Now that we have the lineup, let's get right to it!
January
What is this?
I went to Shinjuku with Rei-chan.
I was walking in Osaka station when I found the real Yoneda2003.
I was so surprised because we both love Yoneda so much!
I was so excited that I called out to him.
And we took her picture.
I didn't even notice.
This is it.
This is really Yoneda 2007.
I'm sure it is!
I've already confirmed it.
It's absolutely true.
A lie.
You two...
They didn't notice.
Not at all.
I didn't tell them.
I didn't tell them... as a fan at all.
I didn't say anything about being a fan.
I was about to say it... and then I thought about it for a second.
It's better to say it, but...
But I wasn't sure about that.
What do you mean?
I'm not sure if I'm a Nogizaka.
They probably don't even know who we are.
I'm not sure I should say anything.
"So...
What do you mean, "So"?
That's a serious response.
I don't get it.
What do you mean, "so"?
That's the end of my information.
But I'm sure 2,000 Yoneda have already gotten the message.
Next time you see him, thank him.
Okay.
Next...
Mr. Umeda.
Ignored by the Cabinet's Bandit Roster.
Wasn't there something about bandits?
That's right.
On the BQ news before...
Ms. Manatsu tried to contact the cabinet registry, but they kept ignoring her.
There was something about that, wasn't there?
Yes, there was.
Something happened back in 2020.
I went to see a concert in December 2022.
I went to see a concert in December 2022, and I liked the book so much that I contacted him.
Thank you very much.
And then in January...
I thought I had contacted you, but when I looked back, you hadn't come back.
And finally, they came back in June, six months later.
Is this it?
That's right.
I don't like it.
I'm the one who said that.
You made me feel bad.
That text scared me, too.
He apologized for everything.
Did he really say that?
No, it's from the book.
I was a guest on the show.
I said, "Oh, you didn't come back.
He said he hadn't been home yet.
I heard from him.
So that's why he came.
I see.
What's this?
All I can do is apologize.
It's for after the concert.
I'm going to take a break and return it the next day.
But I'm so stupid that I forget the next day.
It's a pattern of forgetting.
You've already looked at it once, haven't you?
Yes, I know.
I know, but that's when you're not important.
No, no, no.
It's really sad.
"Not for this person...
It's just so quick.
Thank you before you close?
No, it's not.
I don't know if it's rude to say something like that.
I'm so worried about it that I end up replying later and later.
I'm sorry.
That's great.
It's not just a matter of apologizing.
That's harsh.
If it's your first time, it's not enough.
It's your second time.
I'm sorry.
Are you really sorry?
This is turning into a pretty serious case.
All I can do is apologize.
Yeah, well...
Just say "thank you" and return it right away.
But wouldn't it be rude to just say thank you?
No, it's rude not to return it.
That's right.
Let's continue.
Yamashita, what's this in Okinawa in winter?
Lilia Ito, a member, and I went to Okinawa last New Year's.
So you're from there?
Yes, it's my hometown.
I'm a local, so I was wondering what kind of clothes I should wear.
I heard you need a coat or something.
Yes, that's right.
I was told to wear a jacket, but I believed him and wore a flimsy jacket.
Yes, just as they said.
I went to Kokusai Dori and froze to death.
At that time, Lilia was wearing a very heavy jacket.
Lilia
I went there looking a bit shabby.
I was dressed exactly as you said.
Lilia is wearing very heavy clothes.
Yes, she is.
Maybe it's a difference in the value of the jacket.
Difference?
The jacket.
Yes, there is a difference in the value of the jacket.
I think there's a lot of difference.
I mean, it's a solid jacket.
You mean not like this?
Not like this.
So when you go to Okinawa in January, what's the best way to dress?
Just a jacket.
I don't know how to say it.
I don't know how to say it... but I think it's more like a face on top.
That's why everyone thinks the jacket is important.
It's important!
I'm releasing a new single.
It's different all over the country.
Okay, let's continue.
This way.
What's this?
Asuka went to Asuka in Nara to pray for a hit.
Like a pilgrimage.
With Iroha.
So you went to all the places she went?
Yes, we lifted rocks.
It was in an enclosure.
There's a video.
There's a video of it.
Come on.
Here we go.
Come on. Come on.
Right hand.
I have to do it with one hand.
You just have to lift it up.
It's a wish come true.
Maybe I can wait.
Are you sure?
Maybe I can't.
I can do it. I can do it.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Three minutes.
Help me.
I don't have this.
I don't know, there's a lot of them.
I'll get out from under.
Let's move.
One time.
Maybe it'll work.
What's that?
Can I get in from underneath?
Come on. Come on.
Up, up, up.
It's up. It's up now.
Is that a thing?
Can I put my hand in from the bottom?
No, you can't.
Because that hole doesn't make any sense.
It's going up, it's going up.
It's up.
It's going up, but I don't know what it means.
It's not working.
I feel like this is great.
It's covered with water.
Good job, Okuda.
Good, good, good.
You have to start from there.
It's hard to do.
Amazing, isn't it?
That's the hard part, isn't it? The angle from there.
There it is!
Okuda!
That was just a second!
Ogawa said from under this hole.
That's no good.
Is it bad?
I don't know if it's bad or not, but Mr. Himura said it's not.
I don't know what that hole means...
Oh! There she is!
Are you talking from down there? There...
Yes, that's her...
That's not right, is it?
That's right...
Oh, no, it's not working.
But it's nice. You're going there.
He's a great guy. I mean, I like him.
And it just so happens that a certain Nagi and I were there the same day.
Why, were you working there?
No, I went there on a private trip.
You happened to be in Nara?
Did you two go there? The stone place.
Yes, we did.
Did you? How was it?
We went down there.
Both of you? And you, Nakanishi?
No, I think I went from the top.
You're lying, right?
There's no way you could've made it.
Ogawa's good at B-news.
Didn't he win a grand prize for his umbrella story?
What happened to that?
Nothing happened.
And all kinds of people are saying it's a lie.
If it's a lie, it's horrible!
Then what's this Valentine's Day nightmare?
I wanted to thank everyone for Valentine's Day.
I made over 40 cookies, including the staff's, at home.
Cookies like these!
What is this?
Cookies, cookies from work, pound cake...
Before baking.
That's right, I summoned my brother to do the same thing.
Well, he's in another world, so let's summon him.
We did it together.
We did it together. We did it all the way through.
But on the day of the event, I was so excited that I wanted to go to the site.
But I forgot everything.
Home? What, what, what, why?
I forgot that I'm the type of person who forgets unless it's hanging in the hallway.
I forgot I'm that type.
I forgot.
What's wrong?
So go home and have your brother eat it all.
You're going to eat it all?
Hey...
You're gonna bring it back?
I'm not bringing it!
Let's go on to the next one.
I'm tired of this... this... this... this... this... this...
Are you okay?
No, I'm not okay.
Success means there's a video!
Yes, this is probably the one I told you about during the Halloween project.
I'm not sure if I should show this video here.
Scary!
But it's the first time to show this video, so it's not scary if all of us watch it together.
Let's watch it first without asking any questions.
Please watch the video first.
Yes, sir.
What?
The door is closed.
But here's the thing.
I opened the curtains.
And there's a torii gate.
You mean the gate is rattling?
No, it's not.
I don't know what this means.
The rattling, and the window's closed, so that's weird.
But you'd expect something like that in a big building.
It's haunted.
Is this only happening now?
Yes, it is.
And it won't ring again?
Yes, it does.
I'm mad at it.
Because I'm saying things like, "What the hell is this?
Like it's not a ghost.
But I wish it would come out more clearly.
I'm the one who was doing the "jang-jang".
Glass.
Like "jang-jang".
I was so excited when he brought that.
I'd have been thrilled.
I'm still a B-movie guy.
Well, this is about as good as it gets in AB, I guess.
But this place...
You know...
The other members said it was a little weird.
Everyone had a single room, but there were like four futons on the floor.
That's something from the other side.
Everyone had four futons.
What are you talking about?
That...
It's a person's work.
It was the next one.
Everyone said, "How many sheets did you get?" Everyone said, "Four sheets, four sheets.
I was the only one in my room with six sheets.
What are you talking about?
It means that the person on the other side saw a lot of people.
Everyone else had four.
Why are they so far apart, and why doesn't anyone say, "Why?
But now I'm thinking it's haunted, because there's six cards instead of four.
Like, "Wow, two cards are haunted.
That's not true.
Next...
No, no, no, this is not a spider, this is really not a spider.
I'm sure it's not a spider. This is the one I really got right.
I threw out the first pitch at a wbc running game last year.
There was a lot of video footage of the event, so I thought I'd put it on my sns page.
I was checking the pictures that the manager took.
Then one of the photos was one that I didn't recognize.
I was checking the photos that the manager took.
I have a picture of that too.
Seriously?
That's scary.
What?
Do you recognize it?
Which one?
I don't know where it is.
Take a closer look.
Just a little bit.
Oh, my God!
I don't get it at all.
Oh, my God.
Scary.
I saw your phone screen.
Can I ask you to look at your mom's screen?
I mean, what's wrong with her face?
I don't know who that is.
There's an old lady in there.
What? What is this?
I don't know.
I'm a normal person.
I'm the only one with a screen on my phone.
What is this?
Psychic phenomena.
It's just a coincidence.
Here.
Take this.
Take this. Take this.
This...
Ah.
You.
Me too.
I've got one too.
Oh, yeah?
The music video.
It's a picture of some of us together.
There...
It's mirrored.
Behind you.
What's with the appearance now? I've got it.
Why is it there now? It's none of your business.
Why do you have it? Let me see it in the second half.
That's the best story I've ever heard.
That's great. Go on, then.
Oh, there it is.
She's overreacting.
We had a takoyaki party in my room.
Okamoto and I had a takoyaki party in my room, and we put Okamoto on a sheet so he wouldn't fly away
Okamoto and I had a takoyaki party in my room, but to keep Okamoto from flying off, we put a sheet of oil on the floor.
We put a sheet of oil on the floor and everything.
Here's a picture of it all ready to go.
What's this? Wait a minute, is this outside?
Outside? I don't know. It's starting to look like an incident.
What?
Why did you bring blue sheets?
Individuals don't often have blue sheets.
Go on.
Here you go.
Ume's sorry shoes on her phone.
This was in April, when I was slammed.
I cherish my bath time.
I was going to soak in the bathtub, so I boiled the water and
I had my cell phone in my right hand and bath salts in my left.
I was about to put in the bath salts when I threw my cell phone in the bathtub.
Was I so busy that my attention span was reduced to 30,000?
I'm totally fine, but I'm still in a daze.
I was going to put the trash in the trash can.
I was going to put the trash in the trash can, and I was going to eat a tissue or something.
And then I put it in my right hand.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm tired now.
I was just saying that you eat tissues
You're throwing them away.
You're holding a cell phone in your right hand and a tissue in your left.
You're holding a cell phone in your right hand and a tissue in your left, and you're about to throw it away.
That's the end of it.
It's kind of funny.
It's B grade.
Now, on to the next one.
What's this background?
Shokichi's hand.
Shokichi, right?
Yes, that's right.
I'm in my third year of high school.
Still in high school
Seventeen.
I'm 18.
I turned 18.
I thought I'd be 19 by now.
Not really.
Not much.
I don't think I've changed much.
High school students are amazing.
A teacher who's been taking care of me since I started high school...
I found out that he was going abroad at the beginning of last year.
I couldn't say hello to him.
He left a letter with a friend of mine.
He was a really good teacher.
He used to give me advice and help me a lot.
I thought he must write really good letters.
When I got the letter from my friend
It was tiny...
I'm so glad you called me.
You don't usually call him at all?
I don't.
You don't usually call me
I don't usually, but you wrote a letter to me
It's so tiny!
That's not all of them, is it?
I don't miss you that much.
It's just...
I'm sorry about that.
It's second only to my name.
You're right, of course.
I hope you like it.
It would be bad if it became more familiar than your own name.
Well then... Shokichi for a while, please.
I'm counting on you.
Next...
Just a roller coaster ride.
What do you mean?
I'm really good friends with Kira Masumoto from Sakura-zaka 46.
We hang out a lot.
I wanted to ride the Ferris wheel.
She said let's go to an amusement park.
I was happy with just the Ferris wheel ride.
But Masumoto-chan said she wanted to ride a roller coaster.
She said we went all the way there.
But I didn't want to go on it at all.
Then she said she wouldn't ride it because she would pay for it.
So I decided to go on it.
But then she was really excited.
I told her I wasn't going to ride it anymore.
Kira-chan told me she didn't want to ride the Viking.
Kira-chan said she wouldn't ride it.
I felt so bad, I wanted to leave.
I told her I was leaving.
But she said she'd pay for it.
Kira-chan.
He said he'd pay for the ride.
I said, "Well, if you're willing to pay, that's fine.
That's a terrible idea.
Did you ride the Viking?
Yes, I did.
It was weird.
It was disgusting.
What are you doing?
You're paying me.
I'm just glad you're willing to go that far to ride with me.
You're the worst kind of woman.
And you think like that.
A guy pays her to go out with him.
Then he'll push you away.
Then you're on a roller coaster ride.
They'll pay for it, so they'll get a great ride.
Why do you always go on roller coasters?
That's what he wants.
Go on, then.
Okay.
You're adjusting well to college.
I'm not really getting used to it, but...
I was told to come in comfortable clothes for table tennis.
I thought a T-shirt would be nice, but...
but I didn't have many T-shirts.
But I didn't have many T-shirts, so I thought this would be perfect.
I thought this would be perfect.
I wore it.
I'm a 3rd year student.
I got a comment from a first-year student
I asked her if she went to Asuka-chan's graduation wedding.
She told me that she went too.
I've been to a lot of weddings.
But did you play a role? Did you go to see them?
I didn't go to see her, but I was allowed to go.
I had a hard time answering him.
But he didn't seem to notice me at all.
So, your friends are still the same?
At the university.
I was making julo in the latrine.
It was a sad story.
But then...
I've made progress.
This year we had chilos on the bench
I finally went to the bench.
Alone?
Alone.
That's good.
It's a bench from the bathroom, so there's a big difference.
Yes, it does.
But, you know, toilet to bench.
What?
Well, if you make it a bench.
It's kind of the same thing.
But now that you're out...
I thought it wouldn't look too weird if we stood in line.
I thought it wouldn't look too suspicious if I stood in line.
I buy a little extra.
What?
You have some leftover chilos?
I take them home and eat them.
I'm going to cut some of these into single pieces.
Extra chilos.
That's a sad song.
I'll buy some chilos for my friends.
Wow, Akimoto-san, you're going to do it!
I really think he's going to do it!
Today, we will announce the selected members for the 35th single of Nogizaka46!
Every time a new single is released
Nogizaka46 selects the members who will perform the song each time a new single is released.
The formation for the 35th single is as follows
First, Leno Nakamura in the 3rd row
Next to be called out was
Ayano Yoshida Christy
Yoshida, a 3rd term student, was selected for the first time.
I'm sure it's because of the timing that they chose Yoshida.
I hope to find out what I can do only for myself during this period.
I hope I can find out what I can do only by myself during this period, and I hope I can enjoy the place little by little.
Third row: Hazuki Mukai
Kaede Sato
Ria Ito
Tamami Sakaguchi
Teresa Ikeda
Miku Ichinose
Third row and last is Mao Ioki
followed by 2nd row
Nao Yumiki
Mayu Tamura
Sakira Kawasaki
Nagi Inoue
Haruka Kaki, Sakura Endo
Last row: 1st row, Renka Iwamoto
Hiroki Yoda Minami Umezawa
Shiori Kubo, and the center of the 35th single
are
Thank you very much, Mizuki.
Yamashita, who announced her graduation, became the center for the third time
To be honest, there was a part of me that didn't really care about the position anymore.
But when I was told that I would be the sole center, it was a very sobering feeling.
I am very grateful to be able to take this combination for my last single.
I'm very grateful to be able to take this position on my last single.
I also felt that the third term students, who became the most senior generation in this single, would be
I hope I can become a good senior if I accept it and make it exciting.
It's difficult, but you know what Manako and the others did with cars?
Car action.
I'd like to do something on that level.
Let's do Birch.
I'd like to think of something that I haven't done yet, something that won't kill me.
YamashitaLast single, what kind of colors will you play with your classmates and juniors?
Omorize!
Too much fun!
I'll buy two!
Marizara Ozora!
Wake up!
Does that mean that Endo might create such a thing?
I won't either!
Gokisei's photo book "Ano Kaka Nogizaka ni Ita I Was in Nogizaka" will be on sale on February 20
Birthday Live on sale from Feb. 23
35th Single Online Meet & Greet will be held
I am Rika Yamamoto
I'm Ayano Yoshida Christy
We have our combination name, don't we?
Yes.
What is it?
Seino.
We're the main duo.
Lemon tea... in hiragana.
I play a lot. I'd love to play with you again during the show.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Keep pushing.
Thank you for watching.